David Bromberg collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2. Photographs, manuscripts, and sound recordings, ca. 1962-2013
  - Subseries 4. Group 4, ca. 1967-2011
    - The Integrator, September 25, 1973, manuscript (Box-folder 5/2)
      "In Concert, Bromberg, Sept. 16."
    - Promotional flyer and Encore! Article, 1995, manuscript (Box-folder 5/3)
      Flyer for "David Bromberg's 50th birthday/Big Band Reunion," State Theater, Portland, Maine; "Legendary Performer Celebrating 50th Birthday in Portland."
    - Belize Billboard, November 9, 1967, manuscript (Box-folder 5/4)
      "Phoenix Singers Due This Afternoon: David Bromberg."
    - Promotional flyer, October 6, 1972, manuscript (Box-folder 5/5)
      For "Folk Variations with Phil Ochs, Doc Watson, and Special Guest David Bromberg." Philharmonic Hall, Lincoln Center.
    - The Gazette, October 2008, manuscript (Box-folder 5/6)
      "On the Beat. David Bromberg: The Legacy of Sleepy Hollow."
    - Promotional poster for "The Phoenix Singers," ca. 1967-1968, manuscript (Box-folder 5/7)
    - Photograph of Phoenix Singer, December 24, 1967, manuscript (Box-folder 5/8)
      Photographic print of Phoenix Singers waiting for customs clearance in the airtport at Belem, USIS Belem, Brazil.
    - Cash Box article, April 13, 1968, manuscript (Box-folder 5/9)
      "Talen on Stage: Stone Poems, Jerry Jeff Walker."
    - Schwann-1 Record and Tape Guide, September, 1980, manuscript (Box-folder 5/10)
      2-layer cover illustration.
    - Dial article, March, 1987, manuscript (Box-folder 5/11)
      "Arlo Guthrie Picks and Strums With a Band of Pals."
    - Elo di Locarno, July 8, 1975, manuscript (Box-folder 5/12)
      "David Bromberg Band Al Teatro Dmitri."
    - Crawdaddy, April, 1974, manuscript (Box-folder 5/13)
      "Wanted Dead or Alive: David Bromberg Review."
    - New York Times articles, 1970, manuscript (Box-folder 5/14)
      "Dylan Album Shows Shift in Direction." 16. "Bromberg Shows Style on Guitar."
    - The Village Voice, September 3, 1970, manuscript (Box-folder 5/15)
      "Riffs: A Most Uncommon Festival."
    - Promotional pamphlet for the Folklore Center, ca. 1965-1973, manuscript (Box-folder 5/16)
      Folklore Center Continuing Folk Festival, "First Solo Show," presented by Izzy Young.
    - The Daily News Tarrytown, February 6, 1974, manuscript (Box-folder 5/17)
      "David Bromber's Parents are His No. 1 Fans."
    - New York Post and New York Times articles, 1974, manuscript (Box-folder 5/18)
      "Jam Sessions at Radio City"; "Bromberg Flexes His Musical Muscles."
    - Boston Globe, February 22, 1974, manuscript (Box-folder 5/19)
      "David Bromberg Just Loves Playing."
    - Stereo Review, May, 1973, manuscript (Box-folder 5/20)
      "Recording of Special Merit: Jerry Jeff Walker."
    - Brown Daily, April 25, 1972, manuscript (Box-folder 5/21)
      "Music at Big Mother: David Bromberg."
    - New York Post, May 1, 1972, manuscript (Box-folder 5/22)
      "The Lyons Den."
    - Promotional flyer for Mother Records at Brown University, April 24, 1972, manuscript (Box-folder 5/23)
      "David Bromberg: Folk Guitar Wizard in His Own Right."
    - New York Times article, January 28, 1974, manuscript (Box-folder 5/24)
      "Pop Music: Bromberg, A Complete Entertainer."
    - New York Post concert listing, March 11, 1974, manuscript (Box-folder 5/25)
      Concert listing for Show at Madison Square Garden felt forum.
    - The AU Report, 1974, manuscript (Box-folder 5/26)
      Photo and caption for AU concert performance.
    - New York Times article, January 28, 1974, manuscript (Box-folder 5/27)
      "Pop Music: David Bromberg, Entertainer."
    - Statesman, January 24, 1975, manuscript (Box-folder 5/28)
      "Bromberg and Sebastian: Unlikely."
    - The Village Voice, January 24, 1975, manuscript (Box-folder 5/29)
      "Riffs" review of Mother Earth show.
    - Newspaper advertisement for Town Hall, January 25, 1975, manuscript (Box-folder 5/30)
      "David Bromberg and Friends."
    - New York Times article, August 26, 1974, manuscript (Box-folder 5/31)
      "Bluegrass Plants Roots in Folk Festival."
    - The Village Voice, 1974, manuscript (Box-folder 5/32)
      Review of Town Hall show.
    - Independent-Journal, June 20, 1975, manuscript (Box-folder 5/33)
      "Bromberg in Rare Marin Show."
    - The Jewish Week, September, 1975, manuscript (Box-folder 5/34)
      "Overtones and Undercurrents: Amram and Bromberg, 2 Great Performers."
    - New York Times, July 28, 1973, manuscript (Box-folder 5/35)
      "Nostalgia Lurks at Folk Festival."
    - Billboard, ca. 1973, manuscript (Box-folder 5/36)
      "David Bromberg: Folk City, New York," concert review.
    - The Evening Bulletin, April 2, 1973, manuscript (Box-folder 5/37)
      "Bromberg, Hartford, Watson Perfect for a Rainy Night" via management promotional flyer.
    - The Villager, August 30, 1973, manuscript (Box-folder 5/38)
      "Bromberg at Pier."
    - Newport (RI) Daily News and newspaper ad for Salt in Newport, December, 1973, manuscript (Box-folder 5/39)
      "Songwriter to Perform at Tavern." 43. Newspaper advertisement for Salt in Newport.
    - New York Times articles, 1973, manuscript (Box-folder 5/40)
      "Instrumentalists Dominate Folk Fest." 45. Indians Win One at Folk Festival."
    - The Village Voice, October 4, 1973, manuscript (Box-folder 5/41)
      Advertisement for Brewer and Shipley with David Bromberg at Drew University, Madison, NJ.
    - The Minneapolis Star, June 4, 1973, manuscript (Box-folder 5/42)
      "Bromberg Back with Act to Reckon With" via management promotional flyer.
    - "Quotable Quotes" collection of album reviews, undated, manuscript (Box-folder 5/43)
      Compiled by Fantasy Records.
    - Japanese magazine #007, 2012, manuscript (Box-folder 5/44)
      Root: Route to Music.
    - The Sounding Board: The Official Newsletter of the Martin Guitar Company, July, 2006, manuscript (Box-folder 5/45)
      "M-42 David Bromberg Signature Edition Pays Tribute to the Origin of the Original in Guitars."
    - Acoustic Guitar Magazine, November, 2007, manuscript (Box-folder 5/46)
      "At Home With the Blues."
    - Mad Magazine, April, 2008, manuscript (Box-folder 5/47)
      "The Answer Mad."
    - Mucchio Selvaggio (Italy) n. 25, December, 1979, manuscript (Box-folder 5/48)
      Cover photograph.
    - Frets Magazine, June, 1979, manuscript (Box-folder 5/49)
      "David Bromberg: Moving Into His Own Spotlight."
    - Sing Out! The Folk Song Magazine Vol. 35, No. 2, undated, manuscript (Box-folder 5/50)
      "David Bromberg: More Than Blues... Guaranteed!"
    - People Into Music magazine, August, 1978, manuscript (Box-folder 5/51)
      "David Bromberg: Master of Many Musical Idioms."
    - Melody Maker, August 9, 1975, manuscript (Box-folder 5/52)
      "Bromberg's Out of the Basket."
    - Melody Maker, June 5, 1976, manuscript (Box-folder 6/1)
      "Bromberg: Happy Tradesman."
    - Rolling Stone, March 10, 1977, manuscript (Box-folder 6/2)
      "David Bromberg: The Demon Changes His Disguise."
    - Rolling Stone, April 11, 1974, manuscript (Box-folder 6/3)
      Album Reviews. "Wanted Dead or Alive: David Bromberg."
    - Rolling Stone, July 31, 1975, manuscript (Box-folder 6/4)
      Album Reviews. "Midnight on the Water: David Bromberg."
    - Melody Maker, March 26, 1977, manuscript (Box-folder 6/5)
      Photograph caption from upcoming UK tour.
    - San Francisco Chronicle, July 3, 2004, manuscript (Box-folder 6/6)
      "Datebook: Section E"; "Guitarist David Bromberg Was a Virtuoso on the Bay Area Scene Until He Packed Up in 1980--Now He's Back in Circulation."
    - Collection of press clippings, undated, manuscript (Box-folder 6/7)
    - Japanese newspaper feature on upcoming show, 2012, manuscript (Box-folder 6/8)
    - Tarrytown News, December 8, 1975, manuscript (Box-folder 6/9)
      "Bromberg Has Traded Magic for Music."
    - Westchester Premier Theater playbill, December 9, 1975, manuscript (Box-folder 6/10)
    - David Bromberg collection inventory, undated, manuscript (Box-folder 6/11)
      Item-level numbering for each grouping organized by collection donor.
  - Subseries 5. Group 5, ca. 1962-2013
    - Herald Tribune World Youth Forum Concert NYC, 1962, photographic print (Box 7)
    - David Bromberg performing, ca. 1965-1969, photographic print (Box 7)
    - David Gahr promo shoot, ca. 1970-1973, 3 photographic prints (Box 7)
    - Club Passim, Cambridge, Massachusetts, February 4, 1972, photographic print (Box 7)
    - Mariposa Folk Festival, July 14, 1972, photographic print (Box 7)
      Kenny Kosek and Bukka White in background.
    - Mariposa Folk Festival, 1972, photographic print (Box 3)
    - Mariposa Folk Festival, 1972, photographic print (Box 3)
      Tommy Sheehan, bass; Andy Statman.
    - Oswego State College, 1974, photographic print (Box 7)
      Dick Fegy, David Bromberg.
    - Oswego State College, 1974, photographic print (Box 7)
      Brantley Kearns, Dick Fegy, David Bromberg, Peter Ecklund.
    - Philadelphia Folk Festival, 1973, photographic print (Box 7)
      Left-Right: Kenny Kosek, Larry Packer, Neil Rossi, David Bromberg, and Steve Burge.
    - D. Hoogenbosch photographs of band in Rotterdam and Amsterdam, August 2, 1975, 11 photographic prints (Box 7)
    - Europe tour, ca. 1970-1975, photographic print (Box 7)
      Edinburgh, Scotland. Jay Ungar, Dave Richardson (Boys of the Lough), Richie Giorgano (tour manager).
    - Europe tour, ca. 1970-1975, photographic print (Box 7)
      Edinburgh, Scotland. Ali and Lucy Bain.
    - Europe tour, ca. 1970-1975, photographic print (Box 7)
      Ireland. David Bromberg, Kevin Burke, Richie Giordano.
    - Europe tour, ca. 1970-1975, photographic print (Box 7)
      Nyon, Switzerland. David Bromberg, Jay Ungar.
    - Philadelphia Folk Festival, August, 1975, photographic print (Box 7)
      Mark Precca photograph.
    - David Bromberg, Curt Lindbergh, Danny Counts (bass player), seated, 1976, photographic print (Box 7)
      New York, New York. Mike Tighe photograph.
    - David Bromberg at home, 1976, photographic print (Box 7)
    - David Bromberg at home, 1976, photographic print (Box 7)
    - David Bromberg on Dobro, undated, photographic print (Box 2)
    - David Bromberg, Kenny Kosek, undated, photographic print (Box 2)
      Jim McGuire proof photograph.
    - David Bromberg, undated, photographic print (Box 2)
    - David Bromberg Band, ca. 1977-1978, photographic print (Box 7)
      Bill Kelly photograph. Long Island, New York. Left-Right: John Firmin, Curt Lindbergh, George Kindler, David Bromberg, Dave Shallock, Dick Fegy.
    - Tour picture, Italy, ca. 1980-1989, photographic print (Box 7)
      Left-Right: George Kindler, David Bromberg, Dick Fegy.
    - Promotional band photograph, ca. 1980-1989, photographic print (Box 7)
      John Firmin, Lance Dickerson, Dick Fegy, David Bromberg, Curt Lindbergh, Dave Shallick, George Kindler.
    - David Bromberg, Hugh McDonald, ca. 1980-1989, photographic print (Box 7)
      Wayne Porreca photograph.
    - David Bromberg, Dick Fegy, ca. 1980-1989, photographic print (Box 7)
    - Central Park, NYC photograph, August, 1980, photographic print (Box 7)
      David Bromberg, Nancy Josephson, Paula Lockhart, Rachel Gladstone.
    - David Bromberg, Dick Fegy, 1975, photographic print (Box 2)
      Janet Goldberg photograph.
    - David with Linda Ronstadt radio promo poster, ca. 1980-1989, photographic print (Box 7)
    - Peter Cunningham photograph, ca. 1980-1989, photographic print (Box 2)
    - John Firmin, Margaret Firmin, David Bromberg, ca. 1980-1989, photographic print (Box 7)
    - Group photograph, ca. 1980-1989, photographic print (Box 7)
      Left-Right (back): Richie Giordano (crew), Curt Lindbergh, John Firmin. Front: Lance Dickerson, Dick Fegy, [first name unknown] Miller (tour manager), Melissa Dickerson in front of Lance.
    - Oversize group photograph, ca. 1976-1979, photographic print (Box 2)
      Left-Right (back): Dennis Leonard (sound), Dick Fagy, Hugh McDonald, John Firmin, Steve Mosely. On ground: Curt Lindbergh, "Suds" (bus driver), George Kindler. Back standing: David Bromberg. Front standing: Angus [surname unknown] (crew), Dave Curtin (crew), Ursula Alexander (tour manager), Carol Reed (lighting).
    - David Bromberg on fiddle, ca. 1980-1989, photographic print (Box 7)
      Mike Thut photograph.
    - David Bromberg clapping, ca. 1977-1983, photographic print (Box 2)
      Peter Cunningham photograph.
    - David Bromberg, Dick Fegy, Evan Stover, 1975, photographic print (Box 7)
    - Danny O'Keefe recording session photograph, Atlantic Studios, ca. 1970-1974, photographic print (Box 7)
      David Gahr photograph. Back: David Bromberg, Anita Ball, unidentified, Arif Marden. Middle: Kenny Kosek, Danny O'Keefe, Dr. John (Mac Rebennack). Front: Steve Mosley, Andy Statman, Hugh McDonald.
    - David Bromberg, Morris Stage, Morristown, New Jersey, 1978-11-17, photographic print (Box 7)
      Kevin Papa photograph.
    - David Bromberg, Morris Stage, Morristown, New Jersey, 1978-11-17, photographic print (Box 7)
    - Jay Ungar, David Bromberg, Dick Fegy, 1978-11-17, photographic print (Box 7)
      Morris Stage, Morristown, New Jersey
    - Jeff Wisor, David Bromberg, Gene Johnson, Dick Fagy, ca. 1980-1984, photographic print (Box 7)
      Sarah Anne Shoaf photograph, California, early 1980s.
    - Rutgers University, New Jersey, March, 1976, photographic print (Box 7)
      Kevin Papa photograph. Left-Right: George Kindler, Dick Fagy, David Bromberg, Steve Mosley, Hugh McDonald, Curt Lindbergh, John Firmin.
    - David Bromberg and Lily (dog) in home in Wilmington, Delaware, 2007, photographic print (Box 8)
      Nan L[surname unknown] photograph.
    - David Bromberg at home in Wilmington, Delaware, 2007, photographic print (Box 8)
    - David with National Steel Guitar, 2007, photographic print (Box 8)
      Nan L[surname unknown] photograph. Gift of Phoebe Snow and David Rubinson.
    - David Bromberg on fiddle, 2008, photographic print (Box 8)
    - David Bromberg on guitar, 2008, photographic print (Box 8)
    - Japan tour photograph, 2013, photographic print (Box 8)
      Left-Right: Taro Inove, Mark Cosgrove, David Bromberg, Nate Grower.
    - Japan tour photograph, 2013, photographic print (Box 8)
    - Japan tour photograph, 2013, photographic print (Box 8)
    - Band performing, May 19, 2011, photographic print (Box 8)
      Thomas South photograph. Left-Right, front: Mitch Corbin, Robert Amiot, Josh Kanusky, David Bromberg, Alison Newitt, Kathleen Weber, Nate Grower, Nancy Josephson.
    - David with Signature Guitar and Nancy Josephson, ca. 2013, photographic print (Box 8)
    - Promotional photograph, ca. 2009, photographic print (Box 8)
      Appleseed Recordings, Nashville, Tennessee.
    - Band performing in Tarrytown, 2011, photographic print (Box 8)
      Mike Thut photograph. Tarrytown, New York. Left-Right front: John Firmin, Matt Parker, Peter Ecklund, Curt Lindbergh, Robert Amiot, Josh Kanusky, Alison Newitt, Kathleen Weber, Nancy Josephson.
    - David Bromberg, Mark Cosgrove, ca. 2013-2014, photographic print (Box 8)
    - AARP photograph, ca. 2005-2013, photographic print (Box 8)
      John Firmin, David Brombert, Peter Ecklund, Curt Lindbergh.
    - David Bromberg Band, ca. 2005-2013, photographic print (Box 9)
      Mike Thut photograph. Left-Right: John Firmin, Peter Ecklund, Curt Lindbergh, Josh Kanusky, David Bromberg, Robert Armiot, Mitch Corbin, Nate Grower.
    - Contact sheet from WBAI radio station, NYC, ca. 1960-1969, photographic print (Box 8)
      "Radio Unnamable" - Bob Foss' show. Top row: Bob Foss. Musicians: Jody Stecher (guitar), Winnie Winston (banjo), David Bromberg (guitar). Others unknown.
    - Contact sheet for "Demon in Disguise" record, ca. 1972, photographic print (Box 2)
      Jim McGuire photo shoot.
    - Photo shoot for album, "Wanted Dead or Alive," 1974, photographic print (Box 8)
    - Photo shoot for album, "Wanted Dead or Alive," 1974, photographic print (Box 8)
    - Photo shoot for "Demon in Disguise" record, ca. 1972, photographic print (Box 2)
    - Photo shoot for "Demon in Disguise" record, ca. 1972, photographic print (Box 2)
    - Columbia Records promotional photograph, ca. 1970-1989, 3 photographic prints (Box 8)
    - Magna Artists Corp (booking agent), All-Arts Presentations, Inc., ca. 1970-1989, photographic print (Box 8)
    - Fantasy Records, All-Arts Presentations, Inc., ca. 1970-1989, 4 photographic prints (Box 8)
    - Rounder Records, ca. 1970-1989, photographic print (Box 8)
  - Subseries 6. Group 6: Posters and visual art, ca. 1982-2013
    - Concert poster for the David Bromberg Quintet and Adrien Reju, August 9, 2015, poster (Folder AFC 2015/043: OS01)
      13 x 26 in. poster designed by Gary Houston.
    - Concert poster for the David Bromberg Quintet and Adrien Reju, August 9, 2015, poster (Folder AFC 2015/043: OS01)
    - Concert poster for David Bromberg's Bucket List Birthday Bash, September 19, 2015, poster (Folder AFC 2015/043: OS01)
    - Hand printed poster for Aladdin Theater performance, October 21, 2009, poster (Folder AFC 2015/043: OS02)
      13 x 26 in. poster designed by Gary Houston, signed and numbered.
    - Hand printed poster for Aladdin Theater performance, ca. 2011-2012, poster (Folder AFC 2015/043: OS02)
      13 x 26 in. poster designed by Gary Houston, signed by artist and David Bromberg.
    - Hand printed poster for David Bromberg Quartet tour (Florida and St. Thomas), January, 2013, poster (Folder AFC 2015/043: OS02)
      18 x 24 in. poster. Numbered and signed.
    - Original illustration that became cover artwork for David Bromberg's self titled Columbia Records album, ca. 1972, illustration (Box 10)
      Original artwork.